http://www.cascadevetclinic.com/website-policy

Website Policy | Cascade Veterinary Clinics
Skip to main content
Wenatchee: (509) 663-0793 | East Wenatchee: (509) 884-7121 | Leavenworth: (509) 548-5896 | After-Hours: (509) 665-2233
Website Policy
This page describes information collected on this Web site.
There are two types of information collected on this Web site:
Personally Identifiable Information
In some instances, this web site collects personally identifiable information (such as email address, name, phone number, etc.) This information is only collected when volunteered by the user – for example, when completing a newsletter subscription request form or registering for a class.
Non-personally Identifiable Information
This site also collects non-personally identifiable user information, such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, cookies, Internet tags and navigational data (server log files). This information is used for system management and to improve the content and navigation of the site.
We do not match personally identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information. In other words, we do not link personal information (name, etc.) with visit information, such as pages visited or files downloaded. In effect, all such visit information is anonymous.
Use of Information
We will use the information you submit to improve this web site and to better provide news on services and related news that may be of interest to you. You will only receive an e-mail from us for information you have requested or as confirmation of information that you submitted (i.e. class registration).
Any personally identifiable information you submit to us on any survey, class or event registration, web site feedback form, or for any other form is for exclusive use by this web site or other entities that are involved in the operation or fulfillment purposes of this site. It will not be shared with any other party, except if required by law.
We do not sell, trade or rent personal information about our users.
Acceptance of These Terms
By using this site, you signify your acceptance of the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our web site.
Links to Other Web Sites
This site contains links to other web sites. Please be aware that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any other web site. For your own protection, read the privacy policy of each web site that you visit.
Adherence to Principles
If at any time you believe this site has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by email to cascadevet@cascadevetclinic.com and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem.
Clinic Locations
Wenatchee
(509) 663-0793
Cascade Veterinary Clinic
1201 Walla Walla Avenue
Wenatchee, WA 98801Directions
Hours:
Hours:
Hours:
© 2020 Cascade Veterinary Clinics. All Rights Reserved. Designed and Developed by 3Sherpas.
